https://www.cpap-supply.com/terms_privacy.asp

Evora Compact Nasal Mask
Questions? Call Toll Free:
02/12/16Z1 Trade-In Offer
01/28/16DreamMapper...
01/19/16CPAP Compliance...
08/12/15Benefits of Soft Cloth Masks
05/12/15Nano? Pico? What's Next?
12/18/142014 Top Products
11/7/14ResMed AirView Compliance...
10/17/14Health Savings Account Info
10/6/14CPAP & Medicare
08/27/14ResMed AirSense 10
04/07/14Humidity for Traveling
10/10/13ResMed Protects Patents...
07/18/13Insurance Changes Increase...
05/03/135 Things We Like About the Wisp
03/20/13CPAP Prices and Brand Image
02/20/13A REMstar Plus Lasts 11 Years
12/17/12Prescription for a CPAP Machine
12/13/12Will CPAP Be Taxed?
11/29/12Auto CPAP vs. Standard CPAP
11/14/12CPAP Battery Backup
10/10/12From 50 Series to 60 Series
09/10/12What's With Heated Tubes?
01/12/12Buying CPAP Equipment Securely
01/11/12DeVilbiss Follows Others...
12/21/11CPAP vs. BiPAP
12/14/11CPAP Equipment Online
10/26/11How to Stay Healthy...
10/25/11CPAP Equipment for Women
9/21/11CPAP Machine & Mask Recom...
07/05/11DeVilbiss SmartFlex Effectiveness
05/05/11CPAP Travel Checklist
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.To quickly process your transactions.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Senske CPAP Supply, Inc.. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on August 6, 2003.Questions and feedbackWe welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.Online Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
CPAP-Supply.com
3002 E Bridgeport Ave
Spokane, WA 99207
Toll Free 888-955-2727
Fax 509-448-1540
Company Info
About Us
100% Price Guarantee
Privacy
Terms
Why Shop With Us?
Help
FAQ
Contact Us
Order Status
Ordering
My Rewards Program
Get Connected
Articles
Z1 Auto with Battery
Copyright ©  Senske CPAP Supply, Inc.. All Rights Reserved.Some Images Provided by ResMed © ResMed 2010 Used with Permission.Mask kits are packages of individual mask components which can be purchased without a prescription. If you order a mask kit, you will receive individual mask parts, some of which may have been opened/removed from their original packaging.Built with Volusion
